Oh, no, no, no!
Boom! Boom! boom!
Ta-da!
Pretty colors!
And so it begins!
Nartao this time
Mac!
Video of eating Mac!
I'm going to eat it!
Rather than
Today is actually the day of the filming of this
Teammate's performance
It was the day of the last performance before the suspension
thank you for your hard work
thanks for your hard work!
It was fun, wasn't it?
Today's performance was so much fun!
It went by so fast.
I know they call it the last show before the hiatus, but it didn't feel like it.
But it didn't feel like it.
It didn't.
The last song we sang together...
The last song we sang together was called "Yakusokuyo
With that song, I finally came to feel that it was really the last song.
I finally got the feeling that it was really the last song.
In the midst of all this
It's a little bit of history.
This way...
Ta-da!
I've already mentioned this at the beginning.
Here at MacDonald's...
Mac has just collaborated with One Piece!
I'm so happy!
Thank you!
In such a jam-packed rehearsal period
I'm so happy to have such a healing experience!
You may think I'm going to bed early.
It's true that we really don't have much time left at the end of the show, so we're taking pictures.
That's right.
Feed me.
Let me eat.
"Forgive me, it's late.
It's the end of the show.
Before 10 o'clock.
Around 10 o'clock.
I'll do my best tomorrow.
I'll do my best to digest it.
So I have a concert in a week.
I'll do my best.
I'm going to eat good food and get my mother
Narutao
Seino
Bon appétit!
Here.
I...
It's kind of like this.
It's in a box.
I don't think I've ever had a burger before.
Isn't it cute?
Look at this.
What is it?
Oh, my God! It's so cute!
Do you see it? What's that? It's glowing!
Wait, it says "standing".
Oh, I see it! I see it!
It's totally different!
That's amazing!
He's so cute!
O-roshi!
Oroshi! And this font is really like the font of Don of One Piece!
Maybe it's the same font as this Don's font!
Oh, man!
It's so good! So cute!
Hey, what's up with the picture?
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
It's so cool. I was just playing with the filter earlier.
Yeah, just take the picture.
I'm serious.
Thank you so much! Cute!
That's amazing! It's such a bun!That's amazing! I didn't know they made buns like this!
I've never had a box, box type burger before.
Yeah, the one you're nursing.
Oh my gosh!
So cute!
This is what Luffy used to eat! That's how I feel!
Then, I'll eat it! And the burger too!
Bon appétit!
Wow! Looks so good!
Wow!
Bon appétit!
Mmm!
It's good, but...
Yum!
Delicious!
I've never had chicken before.
It's so good! It's normal.
The fried chicken is fried, right?
The one that is deep fried.
The fried chicken is so delicious and the buns are so delicious!
The buns are so delicious!
I didn't know they were this soft, these swirls!
I think it tastes sweet!
Oh, I know, I know!
It's sweet.
How's it taste? Yuzu?
Yuzu-scented grated yuzu?
Chicken Sticky!
It's also a chicken tadashita!
The yuzu aroma is really delicious!
I thought it would be a little
But it's better than I expected.
Yuzu?
Yuzu is so strong!
Delicious!
It's good. It's...
It stings!
It stings. It stings like a bitch.
I'm so scary macho.
We can do it tomorrow!
Let's do it.
I'll do my best tomorrow.
I wonder what time I'll wake up tomorrow.
I don't...
I don't want to think about it.
You had some wardrobe trouble today, didn't you?
Yes!
Yes, yes, yes.
It just happened.
And the fans.
This part.
Bust.
Bust!
Busty!
Various members wear it all the time.
I've been wearing it a lot.
The size you gave me...
My bust is pretty flat.
I'm jealous of your bust.
I saw in the comments afterwards.
I saw in the comments you said you were about to get a bee in your bonnet.
You found it?
The outfit.
You'd think I'd be stupid enough to think that.
You bee-opened it?
Oh, my God!
During a performance.
Isn't that amazing?
I thought he was right.
He was mad.
Once.
Eight's previous performances.
I'll tell you at a glance.
The Party's About to Start
The performance I missed you
Let's cry at Eight.
And the drops will become rainbows that will lead to the future.
I remember now.
Yes, today.Yeah, today.
I wanted to say this right at the end of the day.
I was trying to say it right at the end today, but I think I said it in a very abbreviated form.
That was a great show.
I thought the music was young.
It's fun... when you're doing it together.
I can see that.
It's so much fun because it's A and we're all doing it together.
The presence of the members is so big
It's fun!
Every song was fun
But then there was the first party performance.
Do you remember that one?
I do.
In the beginning.
But it was August 5th.
August 5th.
You're good at remembering things like that, aren't you?
I always remember the date.
It's important.
I wanted to see you, but I don't remember.
It was the first of September.
Two days?
Maybe the 5th.
I missed you on the first day.
You were there on the first day?
The camp.
I missed you.
It was bittersweet.
I know it was bittersweet.
That's why I wanted to do it.
I said I wanted to play the center role for the first time.
I wanted to do it.
How memorable.
First of all, the party.
You know, the party.
It was a lot of fun being on the road.
It was fun.
I wonder if we can do a traveling show.
I'd love to.
Each group has a different costume, right?
We'd borrow them.
It's all so funny.
It was really fun.
I really enjoyed the different theaters.
Like the sizing.
I mean, when I was at HKT...
When I was at HKT, I had a protruding belly button.
Even now, HKT is a bit of a strange type, isn't it?
But back then, it was like an antebellum style.
Debeso is going around, isn't it?
We were doing the star temperature while doing the star temperature.
It was fun.
At that time, the members who were doing the temperature of the stars
I really felt like the God 4.
That's how we were treated at Stahela.
I was treated that way. I was treated that way.
I wanted to be a classmate.
Surprising.
Really?
But this classmate sings on the 16th beat.
At the time, I couldn't do 16 beats at all.
I kept watching, wondering how they could get this groove.
I kept doing it.
I can feel the ground shaking.
I'm doing this all the time.
It's what I do when I'm moving around.
I miss it.
Back then, I used to wear all these flashy outfits.
The hairstyles.
We used to have so much fun.
I had a bear.
Everyone had bears.
Bears were all the rage for a while.
Eight had a problem where everyone had the same haircut.
If you do this and everyone thinks it's nice and cute.
And then the next time, there would be 3 or 4 girls with the same haircut.
Isn't the hair-cutting cycle the same?
The number of people who cut their hair short increases all at once.
Sometimes more.It can increase.
It's like there are no long people at all.
And sometimes there are so many long people.
I guess they're all doing the same thing.
We get along.
They're really close.
During the first "Let's start the party" performance.
We had only been together for about 3 months.
We made our debut in the theater.
We learned the show right away.
The teacher who was teaching us at the party at the time
He was crying because of how bad Eight was.
He was crying?
I was so sorry that I made her cry, and I was so full of it that I wanted to cry too.
August 5th was the first day of the show, and I was worried even after August started. I was so sorry that I cried so much, but I was worried even in August.
I remember August 1st. So I wondered if we would really be able to go on stage in August.
I thought we were pretty desperate to get on stage. It was true.
It was a tough time. It was tough.
During the rehearsal period for the concert, we would see our old teachers, depending on the piece.
I was happy to hear their comments about how much I had grown up and how much I had matured.
It is a strange feeling that the teachers remain the same as ever.
It makes me realize that I have been a member here for several years.
That's part of it.
After that performance, I started to do a lot of MCing.
I probably started to memorize the script.
That's amazing.
That's great.
It's a lot of work, isn't it?
Yeah, the script.
But thanks to that, and this has nothing to do with the show...
At the very first event in Kumamoto, there were so many MCs.
It's like people from that prefecture do a lot of MCs for events.
I remember I memorized a lot of them.
I didn't miss a single sentence, so it was all in one language.
That's so cute!
Like, "I can't answer this question unless I get this question.
I memorize everything.
That's cute.
She's in a state of memorization.
That's amazing.
I don't know.
You know...
I remember a time when I was like that.
That's amazing.
Oh, wow.
I struggled with it for a long time.
MC.
I struggled with MC'ing.
I didn't speak at all back then.
It's like the moon is turning.
But I don't know, that's good.
Well, you're funny, so it's fine.
All of it.
I think some members are in charge of MCing.
But there are members who are good MCs.
It's a rule.
I also feel like I'm the one who closes things out.
Like I have to organize.
Since I became the captain, I don't think that's a good thing.
It's fine to have members like that.
But if that's all there is, it's too formal.
I want something different to spice things up.
I see.
This MC...
I don't know if you're in charge of MCing.
I don't know if you're in charge of organizing.
I want to hear all kinds of opinions.
That's why I said it's totally fine.
To one of them
One of them.
He says, "You don't have to be so formal about it.
I'm always worried about it.
I'll tell him.
MC, you don't have to worry.
You can say what you think.
Even if it gets a little weird.
I'll fix it.
I'll fix it and leave it with you.
I'm just asking you to speak and be yourself.
I'm listening.
I don't think you have to do that.I don't think you should overdo it.
It's better to be yourself.
Because it's really funny.
But I'm not sure if the fun is coming through.
Stao's...
I think they get it.
No, no, no, it's funnier.
I know it sounds like I'm lifting you up.
But it's true.
It's just...
So I'm just trying to get it out there.
I just want to be able to get it out.
Less.
Let me out.
Yeah, that's fine.
That's a dangerous term.
You can say anything you want, as long as it's not dangerous.
I might say something.
Just keep that in mind.
NARUTAO Channel
I hope you will continue to watch over me. I hope you'll continue to watch over me warmly. I'll be very happy.
By the time the video is uploaded, the concert will probably be over. I'm sure I'll feel refreshed after the concert.
So, until the concert, I'm eating a McDonald's today, and I'm almost done eating,
I'm going to eat, get into the groove, and rehearse hard starting tomorrow to make sure the concert is a good one.
I will do my best to make it a good performance. Thank you for your continued support. Thank you very much.
See you later. See you later. Bye-bye.
Bye!